[EP10]
Why are you mad?
Chu Nanfeng has already left.
This trick doesn't work on me.
I hope it doesn't.
What you know
is that your arm is injured.
What you don't know
is that you're weak.
Do you like
the wild grass outside so much?
Is Chu Nanfeng's car
that comfortable?
I'd rather take his car
than yours.
I can do it myself.
Don't move.
It hurts.
Chu Nanfeng...
He's so mean.
It's badly swollen.
You'd better not meet anyone for a few days.
Young Marshal.
Who is he?
Commander Ling.
Young Madam.
The Old Marshal just got back.
He's still weak, I'll take him to bed.
Wait.
Mr. Chu Nanfeng
sent this gift
to express his regards.
What's the hurry?
If so,
please send me back first.
You will
stay here tonight.
When we met the Old Marshal today,
Ling Shenxing was obviously nervous.
And his fingers have no calluses,
not like a gun holder for years.
Or
he's not the real Old Marshal?
What's Ling Shenxing hiding?
I'm useless.
I didn't expect
you to see your uncle.
There's no uncle in this house.
Only Commander Ling.
Yes.
A gift
from Mr. Chu Nanfeng.
Chu Nanfeng
should have found out my father is an impostor.
Do as planned.
Let the identity of my uncle disappear.
Yes,
I understand.
What are you laughing at?
I'm laughing
that you finally
become a real couple with the Young Marshal.
Tonight,
do your best.
How about
I prepare for you?
It's a good thing.
Do you want it or not?
Have you heard about the Young Marshal's request?
Yes.
The whole mansion
has heard about it.
The Young Marshal
finally accepted the Young Madam.
Humph!
I know
the truth.
Young Madam
put that kind of drug
in Young Marshal's tea.
What kind of drug?
It's to make men...
Young Madam,
I'm just a nobody
in this Ling residence.
I'm afraid I can't
be your respectful servant.
I dare not.
My Lady, please forgive me.
I was just talking nonsense.
I'm so sorry.
I'll punish myself.
Doukou,
are you acting?
You do it.
Twenty times.
Every slap
should be loud enough
so that everyone outside
can hear it clearly.
Ah.
If there's even one
that's not loud enough,
such beautiful hands,
it would be a shame if they were gone.
If you have any complaints about me,
I'm open to a frank discussion.
If I hear you
talking nonsense behind my back again,
you'd better watch your tongue.
Mom, try this.
Shrimp with green beans.
I specially asked the kitchen to make it for you.
Try it.
You too.
Madam.
You are kind and generous.
You must help Doukou.
What happened?
Doukou
threw herself into the well.
What?
She was forced to do that by the Young Madam.
How could she do that?
Amitabha Buddha.
Su Muwan,
Willow said
you beat Doukou for no reason.
Not only did you beat her face swollen,
but also forced her to throw into the well.
What happened?
Young Madam
was dissatisfied with Miss Ye's coming to the mansion.
So she took it out on us servants.
Yesterday in the living room,
Doukou just bumped into her by accident.
She forced me to slap Doukou.
She also said that
if I didn't slap hard enough,
she would break my hand.
Doukou felt humiliated,
and in despair,
she jumped into the well.
Willow,
you're really good at making things up.
Doukou is already dead,
and there's no one to prove it.
Young Madam can say whatever
she wants now.
Nonsense!
My sister would never do such a thing.
Madam,
please don't believe her.
Cardamom
is naturally impetuous.
Maybe
she accidentally fell into the well herself.
Don't misunderstand her.
Humph.
Misunderstand?
Su Muwan has always been lawless.
It's not surprising that she did this.
There are laws in the country,
and rules in the family.
Fuyuan.
Yes, Madam.
Did Young Madam really mistreat the servant
and force her to throw herself into the well?
Then do as she did.
Force her to kneel in the garden,
and slap her face.
Madam,
if this gets out,
it will be known that she killed a servant.
It will affect the reputation of the Ling Family.
Reputation?
She did such a thing.
Not to mention slapping her,
it's not too much to kick her out of the Ling Family.
Our Ling Family
will never tolerate such a cruel daughter-in-law.
Don't.
Mom.
This matter
might not be true.
How about this?
Young Madam,
go apologize to Doukou's family now.
We'll
pretend it never happened,
and save our family's reputation.
This isn't over.
You can't just pin this on me.
Don't you even think about it.
Madam,
may I have a word
with Willow?
Go ahead.
You said Doukou bumped into me
and you were ordered to slap her.
I admit it.
But I remember
it wasn't in the living room,
but in the garden.
Yes,
it was in the garden.
Yesterday,
under the magnolia tree in the garden,
Doukou bumped into you.
Oh.
Yesterday, the Young Marshal invited guests,
and ordered servants not to wander around.
Why were you and Doukou in the garden?
No.
I didn't go to the garden.
So where did this happen,
the living room or the garden?
I...
Madam,
it's pretty clear.
She spread rumors about me,
so I punished her.
But to frame me
for her death,
I won't admit it.
But
where is Doukou's body?
Since you keep saying
Doukou jumped into the well,
there must be corresponding marks on her body.
We can find out by examining the body.
Sister,
you're too brazen.
The Old Madam eats vegetarian and recites the Buddha's name.
How can you let the Buddha
see
such
impure things?
Buddha is merciful,
and will clear our names.
He will surely
agree to this.
How dare you!
Autopsy, huh?
Alright, Young Madam.
Tell me,
how do you want to proceed?
A drowning victim
would have significant water in their lungs,
but if the body was dumped,
there wouldn't be any water in the lungs.
Additionally,
struggles would leave marks on the body.
Likewise,
the perpetrator would likely
sustain injuries during the struggle.
So,
why not check for any
unexplained injuries among the servants?
That would reveal the truth, wouldn't it?